[{
    "theme": "¿Sigues traduciendo en tu cabeza?",
    "langread": "en",
    "questions": [{
            "question": "experiment",
            "answers": ["experimentan"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to try, to attempt",
            "answers": ["intentar"]
        },
        {
            "question": "a flea",
            "answers": ["una pulga"]
        },
        {
            "question": "thumb",
            "answers": ["pulgar"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to find",
            "answers": ["encontrar"]
        },
        {
            "question": "level",
            "answers": ["nivel"]
        },
        {
            "question": "especially, above all",
            "answers": ["sobretodo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "tricks",
            "answers": ["trucos"]
        },
        {
            "question": "head",
            "answers": ["cabeza"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to postpone",
            "answers": ["posponer"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to ask (a question)",
            "answers": ["preguntar"]
        },
        {
            "question": "then",
            "answers": ["entonces"]
        },
        {
            "question": "how do you say",
            "answers": ["come se dice"]
        },
        {
            "question": "endings",
            "answers": ["terminationes"]
        },
        {
            "question": "long",
            "answers": ["largas"]
        },
        {
            "question": "atmosphere",
            "answers": ["atmósfera"]
        },
        {
            "question": "theater",
            "answers": ["teatro"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to translate",
            "answers": ["traducir"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to absorb",
            "answers": ["absorber"]
        },
        {
            "question": "inside",
            "answers": ["dentro"]
        },
        {
            "question": "strong",
            "answers": ["fuerte"]
        },
        {
            "question": "to understand",
            "answers": ["entender"]
        },
        {
            "question": "ambitious",
            "answers": ["ambicioso"]
        }
    ]
}]